Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- Directors & Department Chairpersons, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Directors & Department Chairpersons, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Directors & Department Chairpersons, 1984-85 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- COMEPP- Manufacturing Engineering & Productivity Program- Proposals (Box 74, Folder 1)
- COMEPP- Manufacturing Engineering & Productivity Program- to 6/30/83 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- COMEPP- Manufacturing Engineering & Productivity Program-, July 1, 1983-June 30, 1985 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- COMEPP- Manufacturing Engineering & Productivity Program-, July 1, 1985-June 30, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- COMEPP- Manufacturing Engineering & Productivity Program-, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Dynamatron -, 1966-1969 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Dworsky, Leonard -, 1974-1986 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Directors & Department Chairmen Meetings to 6/30/82 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Directors & Department Chairmen Meetings, July 1, 1982-June 30, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Directors & Department Heads, 1981-1982 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Directors & Department Heads, 1960-1980 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Directors & Department Chairmen, July 1, 1982-June 30, 1984 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Commencement, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Commencement, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Commencement, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Commencement, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Commencement, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Commencement, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Commission Independent Colleges and Universities in New York State, 1985 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Commission on Undergraduate Education, July 1, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Communication Arts, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Community College Program, 1969-1975 (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Community Symposium, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Compensation (Extra), 1962 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Composite Materials Program Executive Committee, November 1969 (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Computer, 1965-1968 (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Computer, 1969-1973 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Computer Graphics: CAD/CAM- Consortium, University of Virginia, et al, June 10, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Computer Graphics: CAD/CAM- Consortium, University of Virginia, et al, June 10, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Computer Graphics CAD/CAM- Consortium, University of Virginina, et al, 1981 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Computer Graphics CAD/CAM- Consortium, University of Virginia, et al, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Computer Graphics CAD/CAM- Consortium, University of Virginia, et al, 1983-1984 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Computer Graphics, July 1, 1984-June 30, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Computer Graphics, July 1, 1981-June 30, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Computer Graphics, June 1980-June 1981 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Computer Graphics Proposals, 1980-1981 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Computer Graphics Proposals, 1981-83 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Computer Science Department, January 1986-July 1, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- Computer Science Department, July 1, 1984-December 11985 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Computer Science Department, July 1, 1982-June 30, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Computer Science Department, July 1, 1981-June 30, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Computer Science Department, July 1, 1978-June 30, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Computer Science Department, July 1, 1972-June 30, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Computer Science Department, June 30, 1972-1984 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Office of Computing Services- OCS, 1970-1988 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- University Computer Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Computer Usage Committee, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Computing, 1973-1979 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Computing Center, 1964-1967 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Computing Equipment Grants- Proposals (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Computing Software- Annapolis Conference. Perlis, Alan J. (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Conference: A Cornell Perspective on Learning (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Combustion Institute Conference August, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Engineering Conference, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Consortium (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Consulting Engineers (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Continuing Education (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Engineering Convocation (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Engineering Alumni Convocation, May 2-4, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Convocation, Engineering, May 3-5, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Convocation - New York, April 1976 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Cook, Alice - Ombudsman, 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Cook, Constance E., 1971-1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Cool, T. Professor, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Cooperative Education, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Cooperative Program, Engineering, 1962-June 20, 1979 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Core Curriculum Summer Study, June 1968 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - General, 1966-1979 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Special (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Cornell Associates, 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Cornell Center for Highway Research, 1957 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Cornell Center for Highway Safety Research, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Cornell Clubs Misc., 1970-1979 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Cornell Club Trips/ Meetings with Alumni, July 1, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Cornell Computing Center, 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Cornell Day (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Cornell Experiment Station, 1959 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- "Cornell Engineer", 1959-1960 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Cornell Engineer, 1962-1970 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Cornell Fund Acknowledgement Letters, January 1, 1990-June 30, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Cornell Fund Acknowledgement Letters, April 1, 1989-December 30, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Cornell Fund Acknowledgement Letters, April 1987-April 1989 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Cornell Acknowledgement Letters, May 1986-December 1986 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Cornell Acknowledgement Letters, January 1987-March 1987 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Cornell Acknowledgement Letters, January 1986-April 1986 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Cornell Acknowledgement Letters, December 1984-December 1985 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Cornell Indicators, 1976-1978 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Cornell Indicators, 1979-1981 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- "E" (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Earth Resources Satellite Data, Center for (McNair, Geotech, etc.) (Box 79, Folder 8)
- CRF (Eastman) Patent (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Eaton Yale & Towne (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Economic Opportunity Act (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Economic Status of the Faculty (Box 79, Folder 12)
- E.C.R.C. (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Educational Development Resources (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Eisenhower College - DOD Software Research Institute (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Electric Car Race (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Electrical Engineering Centennial (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Electrical Engineering Re: Director Search (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1988-June 30, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 19)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1985-June 30, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1983-January 1, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1982-December 31, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1983-June 30, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Electrical Engineering, School, February 1982-June 30, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1981-January 30, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, January 1981-June 1981 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1980-December 1980 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, February 1, 1980-June 30, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Electrical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1979-June 30, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Electrical Engineering, July 1978-June 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Electrical Engineering, July 1, 1974-June 30, 1978 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Electrical Engineering, July 1, 1972-June 30, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Electrical Engineering, March 1971-June 30, 1972 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Electrical Engineering Semiconductor Facility (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Electron Microscope (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Emerson Electric Co., June 30, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Energy, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Energy, 1975-1980 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Energy Program, 1973-1975 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Engineering Colleges, 1960-1973 (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Engineering College Council - General, July 1, 1974-June 30, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 12)
- "Engineering @ Cornell", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 13)
- Engineering Graduate School, 1959-1957 (Box 81, Folder 14)
- Engineering Math Book Cranch, Block, Hilton, Walker, 1963-1978 (Box 81, Folder 15)
- Engineering Physics, 1963-1968 (Box 81, Folder 16)
- Engineering College Study, 1963-1964 (Box 81, Folder 17)
- Engineering Cornell Quarterly, July 1, 1964-February 30, 1974 (Box 81, Folder 18)
- Engineering Faculty Memos to July 1, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Engineering Manpower Commission Selective Service Questionnaires, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Engineering Manpower Commission of Engineers Joint Council, 1968-1985 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Engineering Manpower Commission Surveys, 1968-1980 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Correspondence- Eng Quad Sundial, 1979-1982 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Engineering Development Program, 1956-1961 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Engineering Needs, 1965-1972 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Engineer's Week, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Engineering Women's Club, 1971-1987 (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Enrollment Data, 1957-1962 (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Enrollment National (Box 82, Folder 11)
- Entrepreneur of the Year Program, July 1, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- Associate Dean Environment, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- Environmental Problems, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- Center for Environmental Research, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Center for Environmental Research, 1978-1980 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Center for Environmental Research, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Environmental Systems Department, 1966-1970 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Center for Environmental Systems Engineering, 1964-1970 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Ericksen, J.L., 1964-1965 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Erickson, W.H. (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Enzyme Center, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Equipment Needs, 1964-1971 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Esrig, M.I., 1969 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- Everhart, Thomas E., 1984-1988 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Everhart, Thomas E., 1981-1983 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- Everhart, Thomas E., 1978-1980 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Everhart, Thomas E. Misc. Expense Accounts (Box 83, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Eng Expense Accounts, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 15)
- T.E. Everhart Spring Dinners for Dir. & Dept. Chairmen, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 16)
- T.E. Everhart Travel, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 17)
- Everhart Reception, February 19, 1979 (Box 83, Folder 18)
- E.W.A., 1966-1968 (Box 83, Folder 19)
- Extramural Courses, 1958-1961 (Box 83, Folder 20)
- Experimental Engineering Education Program, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 21)
- Extramural Teaching, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 22)
- Exxon, 1980-1981 (Box 83, Folder 23)
- Exxon, 1976-1979 (Box 83, Folder 24)
- "F", 1969-1971 (Box 83, Folder 25)
- Facilities Management Committee (Box 83, Folder 26)
- Facilities Needs for Research (Box 84, Folder 1)
- College of Engineering Faculty Call to Meetings, 1969-1979 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- College of Engineering Faculty Call to Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Faculties Leaves, Courses, etc., 1956-1976 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Admissions and Standards, 1971-1984 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Core Curriculum Committee, 1971-1981 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Division of Basic Studies, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- College Program, 1972-1981 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Faculty Advisory Committee, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Fuertes Memorial Speaking Contest, 1967-1972 (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- General, 1961-1980 (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Liaison Committees, 1970-1971 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Engineering College Faculty- New Faculty, 1972-1982 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Nominating Committee, 1971-1983 (Box 84, Folder 14)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Physics Courses for Engineers 1971 (Box 84, Folder 15)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Scheduling Committees, 1951-1968 (Box 84, Folder 16)
- Engineering Faculty Committees- Silent Hoise & Crane Co. Contest, 1965-1973 (Box 84, Folder 17)
- Faculty Council, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 18)
- Faculty Internships in Industry, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 19)
- Faculty Minutes- Individual Schools, 1957-1958 (Box 84, Folder 20)
- Fairchild Talk, April 1, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 21)
- Fairhurst, C.H. (Box 84, Folder 22)
- Federal Support for Education, 1958 (Box 84, Folder 23)
- Fedora, Ronald Paul (Box 84, Folder 24)
- Fedorov, V.V. (Box 84, Folder 25)
- Fees, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 26)
- Fellowship- Journalism, 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 27)
- Fellowships- NDEA, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 28)
- Fellowships, Scholarships, Assistantships, 1961-1971 (Box 84, Folder 29)
- Fellowships, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 30)
- Field Projects Directory, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 31)
- Financial Aid Undergraduate, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 32)
- Finger Lakes Ventures Fund I- The Pittsford Group (Box 84, Folder 33)
- College Center of Finger Lakes, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 34)
- Five Year Plan, A Position Paper by Dean Everhart, "Towards the 21st Century", 1980 (Box 84, Folder 35)
- Fleming, Joseph E. (Box 84, Folder 36)
- Florida A&M University COOP Program, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 37)
- Fluid Mechanics Curriculum Committee, 1964-1967 (Box 84, Folder 38)
- Fluid Power National Association, 1967 (Box 84, Folder 39)
- Prospects- (Ford), 1955-1963 (Box 84, Folder 40)
- The Ford Foundation, 1960-1977 (Box 84, Folder 41)
- Forecast 1964 Directors- Hypo I (Box 84, Folder 42)
- Forecast- 1964 Directors- Hypo. 3 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Forecast- 1964 Directors- Hypo. 4 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Forecast- 1964 Working Papers (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Forecast- 1964 Submission (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Foreign Students, 1954-1962 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Foster, John (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Foundry Ed. Fdn., 1958-1960 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Free, Ledger (Box 85, Folder 8)
- Freeze- Wage Price, 1971 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- Freshman Engineering Courses Committee ad hoc, April 1970 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- Freshman Grades, 1960-1962 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Freshman Information, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 12)
- Freshman Tutorial Plan, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 13)
- Freshman Seminars for Engineers w/ Arts (writing), 1974-1976 (Box 85, Folder 14)
- Fu, K.S. (Box 85, Folder 15)
- Fuertes Observatory, 1970-1972 (Box 85, Folder 16)
- Fung, Yuan-Cheng Bertram (Box 85, Folder 17)
- Academic Integrity Board, 1975-1986 (Box 85, Folder 18)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology (ABET), 7/86-8/86 (Box 85, Folder 19)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology (ABET), September 1986-May 1987 (Box 85, Folder 20)
- Acheson, Howard, Mrs. (Box 85, Folder 21)
- Engineering Admissions, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 22)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology (ABET), July 1, 1985-June 30, 1986 (Box 85, Folder 23)
- Engineering Admissions, July 1, 1984-June 30, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 24)
- Africana Studies & Research Center, 1985 (Box 85, Folder 25)
- Agricultural Engineering, Department, July 1, 1983-1988 (Box 85, Folder 26)
- Ahl, David (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Air Products & Chemicals Corp., 1981-1990 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Alumni Office- Homecoming Etc., 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- American Association of Engineering Societies Ing, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Annual Report, 1981-1982 (Box 86, Folder 9)
- Annual Report, 1980-1981 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1979-1980 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- Annual Report, 1978-1979 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- Annual Report, 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Annual Report, 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Annual Report, 1975-1976 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- Annual Report, 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- School of Applied & Engineering Physics, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- School of Applied & Engineering Physics, July 1, 1985-June 30, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Applied Mathematics July, 1983-1988 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- College of Architecture, 1968-1989 (Box 86, Folder 22)
- American Society for Engineering Education (ASEE) Summary, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 23)
- American Society for Engineering Education (ASEE), 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 24)
- American Society for Engineering Education (ASEE), 1985 (Box 86, Folder 25)
- ASEE General, July 1, 1988-December 30, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 26)
- ASEE General, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 27)
- ASEE Research & Graduate Study Directory, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 28)
- ASEE Research & Graduate Study Directory, 1987-1988 (Box 86, Folder 29)
- ASEE Research & Graduate Study Directory, 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 30)
- ASEE Research & Graduate Study Directory, 1985-1986 (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Association of Engineering Colleges of New York State - Meeting at Cornell, April 17-18, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Association of Engineering Colleges of NYS -, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Association of Engineering Colleges of NYS -, July 1, 1986-December 31, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 4)
- Association of Engineering Colleges of NYS -, January 1, 1987-June 30, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Ballantyne, Joseph (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Barr, John Henry Memorial Fund (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Bender, Meyer (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Bendix Corp. (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Berens, Mary (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Cornell University Biotechnology Program Research Directory, 1986-1987 (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Center for Advanced Technology for Biotechnology (Agriculture) Annual Report, July 1986-June 1987 (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Center for Advanced Technology for Biotechnology (Agriculture) Annual Report, July 1985-June 1986 (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Biotechnology Institute Executive Board, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1989 (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Biotechnology Institute Executive Board, 1985-December 5, 1986 (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Budget - (Capital Budget Process), 1986 (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Jorge Calado (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Call, D. Computer Committee (Task Group on Computing Concerns), 1983-1984 (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Carnegie Institution, 1981-1989 (Box 87, Folder 19)
- CIA Information, 1981-1988 (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Budget Materials - College of Engineering, 1987-1991 (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Budget Materials - College of Engineering, 1981-1986 (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Center for Environmental Research, July 1985 (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Center for Environmental Research, September 1985-March 1987 (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Re: Chemical Microscopy- letters from alumni Chamot Fund- Walter McCrane (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1989-December 30, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1988-January 1, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1987-June 30, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1987-June 30, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1986-December 30, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, July 1, 1985-December 30, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Chemical Engineering, School of, January 1, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 88, Folder 10)
- China, People's Republic of, January 1, 1982-July 12, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1993 (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1991 (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, September 1990-December 1990 (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, January 1990-August 1990 (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1988 (Box 88, Folder 18)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1987 (Box 88, Folder 19)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, July 1, 1985-December 30, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, July 1, 1984-June 30, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Dean, Arthur H. (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Defense Research & Engineering, Office of, 1960-1963 (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Degree Designations Committee, Ass'n Enginieering Colleges, New York State, 1961-1964 (Box 89, Folder 5)
- "E", 1960-1961 (Box 89, Folder 6)
- "E-F", 1959-1963 (Box 89, Folder 7)
- E.E. Directorship (Search Committee), 1962 (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Electrical Engineering, 1957-1965 (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Ellenwood, F.O. Memorial Book Fund, 1948-1959 (Box 89, Folder 10)
- ECRC- Research Relationships Between Industry & Eng. Colleges (Conference), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Ecuador- Escuela Politecnicia Nacional (AID Program), 1970 (Box 89, Folder 12)
- EDP- Engineering Development Program Sept 1965 (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Education, Research & Development Center, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Engineering Joint Council, 1960-65 (Box 89, Folder 15)
- EJC Panama Conference, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Engineering Women's Club Directory (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Engineering Physics & Materials Science, 1962-1964 (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Engineering Physics (Ad Hoc Committee), 1965-1966 (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Engineering Physics, 1959-1965 (Box 89, Folder 20)
- Engineering Retreat, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Engineering Research Laboratory, 1960-1972 (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Enrollment, 1959-1964 (Box 89, Folder 23)
- Enrollment Estimates, 1938-1960 (Box 89, Folder 24)
- "F", 1960-1964 (Box 89, Folder 25)
- Faculty Incentive Plan, February 9, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 26)
- Ford Foundation Grant Congratulations, May 1961 (Box 89, Folder 27)
- Ford Fellowship (Loans) Questionnaires, 1961-1965 (Box 90, Folder 1)
- Ford Foundation 1960 Proposal (Box 90, Folder 2)
- Ford Foundation Grant, 1960 (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Ford Foundation, 1958-1960 (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Ford Foundation, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Ford Foundation Buildings, 1961-1962 (Box 90, Folder 6)
- "G", 1959-1963 (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Engineering Division of Graduate School, 1956-1964 (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Grumman Remodeling (Box 90, Folder 9)
- "H", 1959-1963 (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Jay E. Hedrick- Placement, 1966-1975 (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Henisch, H.K., 1960 (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Herald Comission (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Hollister, S.C., 1966-1973 (Box 90, Folder 14)
- IBM, 1959-1969 (Box 90, Folder 15)
- International, 1965-1970 (Box 90, Folder 16-17)
- Issues Course, 1960-1963 (Box 90, Folder 18)
- Ithaca Public Schools Report, 1958-1959 (Box 90, Folder 19)
- "K", 1960-1963 (Box 90, Folder 20)
- "J-K", 1959 (Box 90, Folder 21)
- "I-J", 1960-1965 (Box 90, Folder 22)
- "L", 1960-1963 (Box 90, Folder 23)
- "M" (Box 90, Folder 24)
- D.W. Malott (Box 90, Folder 25)
- Materials Science & Engineering, 1961-June 1974 (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1963-1974 (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Mechanical Engineering Associate Dean, 1968-1971 (Box 91, Folder 3)
- M.E. Reorganization (Associate Dean) (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Middle East Technical University, 1964-1966 (Box 91, Folder 5)
- Metallurgical Engineering, 1958-1963 (Box 91, Folder 6)
- Mechanical Engineering, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 7)
- Minority Eductaion, 1973-1977 (Box 91, Folder 8)
- Middle States Association (Box 91, Folder 9)
- MIT, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 10)
- MIT-Cornell Conference, 1955-1957 (Box 91, Folder 11)